<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>A Pelican Blog - EzPz</title><link href="https://thomasmns.github.io/EzPzDev/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://thomasmns.github.io/EzPzDev/feeds/ezpz.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://thomasmns.github.io/EzPzDev/</id><updated>2018-12-25T00:04:55+00:00</updated><entry><title>Merry Christmas!</title><link href="https://thomasmns.github.io/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/merry-christmas" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-12-25T00:04:55+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-25T00:04:55+00:00</updated><author><name>MilkN2Sugars</name></author><id>tag:thomasmns.github.io,2018-12-25:/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/merry-christmas</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I hope everyone has a wonderful Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html"></content></entry><entry><title>Internal Links</title><link href="https://thomasmns.github.io/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/internal-links" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-19T23:37:41+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-19T23:37:41+00:00</updated><author><name>MilkN2Sugars</name></author><id>tag:thomasmns.github.io,2018-11-19:/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/internal-links</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've added internal links to all existing guides to make navigating around easier. For example, if a quest is listed as a prerequisite, you can now click it to find out more information. I've also tweaked some URLs to make things more consistent. For example, game hubs can be reached at both /game and game/index. Links around the site now use the former, simpler syntax.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html"></content></entry><entry><title>About and Contact Pages</title><link href="https://thomasmns.github.io/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/about-and-contact" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-18T23:16:34+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-18T23:16:34+00:00</updated><author><name>MilkN2Sugars</name></author><id>tag:thomasmns.github.io,2018-11-18:/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/about-and-contact</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have (finally!) got around to setting up the &lt;a href="https://thomasmns.github.io/about.html"&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://thomasmns.github.io/contact.html"&gt;Contact&lt;/a&gt; pages. Say hi!&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html"></content></entry><entry><title>Comments and Favicons</title><link href="https://thomasmns.github.io/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/comments-and-favicons" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-11T23:06:29+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-11T23:06:29+00:00</updated><author><name>MilkN2Sugars</name></author><id>tag:thomasmns.github.io,2018-11-11:/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/comments-and-favicons</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've finished adding comments and favicons. Click read more for the details.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the lack of update yesterday, I was in the process of adding a comments system. This has now been finished. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to use Disqus as the comments system. In my experience, Disqus is generally very popular. I've actually seen sites implement a custom comments system, and people ask them to move to Disqus instead as they prefer it - they must be doing something right. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've set Disqus to only load when a button is clicked, so the impacts on page load time should be minimal. If you're not interested in comments, they won't impact you. I've also enabled guest posting, so while you do need to provide an email address (unfortunately I can't change this), you won't need to register for a Disqus account. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really hope you enjoy the comments system. I know some sites have been moving away from comments in recent years, but I think having a sense of community on a site is great. I'll be responding to all messages as soon as I can, so please do feel free to ask questions, make suggestions, point out mistakes and anything else! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disqus does require JavaScript. For those who prefer to browse the web with JS disabled, I'll be adding some alternative contact methods in the coming days (probably a contact form and email address) so you can still get in touch. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news, I've finally added favicons. I've used the awesome &lt;a href="https://realfavicongenerator.net"&gt;Real Favicon Generator&lt;/a&gt;, so the icons should look good across all browsers, when pinned to your phone homescreen and anything else. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The finishing touches on the site should be finished in the next couple of days, then back to writing content! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for visiting as always. &lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>All Games Button Fixed</title><link href="https://thomasmns.github.io/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/all-games-button-fixed" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-09T11:01:42+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-09T11:01:42+00:00</updated><author><name>MilkN2Sugars</name></author><id>tag:thomasmns.github.io,2018-11-09:/EzPzDev/ezpz/news/all-games-button-fixed</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Little bit embarrassing, but turns out the "All Games" button on the homepage wasn't linking anywhere, whoops. All fixed now.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html"></content></entry></feed>